outsourcingroom.com 2010-01-25

# Outsourcing Room :: Services : Private policy

_Privacy Statement for OutsourcingRoom.com_ OutsourcingRoom.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: OutsourcingRoom.com.

For each visitor to OutsourcingRoom.com web site, our web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name, but not the e-mail address. OutsourcingRoom.com collects only the domain name, but not the e-mail address of visitors to our web site, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations. The information we collect is used to improve the content of our web site, used to notify consumers about updates to our web site, not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.

If you supply OutsourcingRoom.com with your postal address on-line you will only receive the information for which you provided us your address. Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers on-line will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed on-line.

Personally Identifiable Information-When visiting OutsourcingRoom.com 's or any Client's Web site and signing up for or using OutsourcingRoom.com services through any Service Page, you may choose to supply OutsourcingRoom.com with information that identifies users personally. For End-Users (Suppliers of Service), this information may include name and contact information, gender, birth date, occupation and industry, shipping and billing information, credit card numbers and other payment information, behavior patterns, purchase history, and other information.

From time to time, OutsourcingRoom.com may use customer information for new, innovative and unanticipated uses not previously disclosed or described in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to the OutsourcingRoom.com web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses or changes. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our web site periodically.

Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by contacting us here. Upon request we provide site visitors with access to all information [including proprietary information] that we maintain about them.

Aggregate Information - OutsourcingRoom.com collects non-identifying, general, generic and aggregate information to better design our Web site and services, and shares the aggregate data with advertisers and other third parties. With respect to security: OutsourcingRoom.com uses industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer and transaction data exchanged with our site.

**Cookies**  
Our Site uses cookies to save your login and password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. If you click the "sign out" link the cookies will be cleared.

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. OutsourcingRoom.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Public Forums**  
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. No one can view your account information without your password, which you can change anytime you want. Personal payment information, such as credit card numbers, are handled by our secure payment processors and are not stored on OutsourcingRoom.

**E-mail**  
To enhance your experience as a Site member, we send out message notifications, newsletters and site announcements, and from time to time third party offers from companies that we feel may have something that will benefit you. Our site provides you with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving different types of communications (except system communications, or communications required for account maintenance), and each email that we send out has a method for opting-out located at the bottom of the message.

**Affiliates**  
We may share some or all of your Personal Information with any subsidiaries, joint ventures or other companies under a common control (collectively, "Affiliates"), in which case we will require our Affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy.

**Business Transaction**  
If our company or our assets related to the Site are acquired by another company, we will attempt to notify you so that you may make an informed decision about this new use of your personal information.

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please [contact us](mailto:outsourcing@cbsystematics.com).
